You haven’t changed.
I learnt that from you.
Stop.. Stop..
Stop.. stop..
Stop! Stop!
Hello.. control room.
I can bet Rs.10, 000. They won’t catch up with me. -Game.
I told you they wouldn’t be able to catch up with us.
Ten thousand…
What happened to your bet?
It’s my turn to bet Rs. 10,000.
These policemen will escort us.
What? -Get out of the car.
How dare you speed away without stopping?
Are you drunk?
I don’t drink. -Blow!!
Blow it properly.
What’s this, sir? Will you kill me?
Won’t you help an innocent?
Look at him...
he’s critical. I’m taking him to the hospital.
He can’t even move his limbs.
Look at him, sir.
Did you see that? If anything happens to him,
I’ll tell the media that you are responsible.
No, sir. Please check. I’ll go only after that.
Go away! -No, sir. Please check. I’ll go only after that.
Go away. Leave! Why are you dragging it?
Get into the car, Take him to the hospital.
Hey, bring the car.
Are they escorting us?
I suggest, we’ll go ahead.
You follow us. We’ll clear the road for you.
Is that okay? -Yes.
Good, Just follow us.
Turn on the siren, sir.
Hey, turn on the siren.
Stop. They left.
You acted very well. -Learnt it from you, right?
I win 20,000. -Alright.
I just have one childhood wish...
-To be escorted by the cops. It’s finally fulfilled.
The inspector is coming. -What?
The inspector is coming!
Is he all right? -Ok sir..
Bring a stretcher?
-Please don’t trouble yourself.
I will manage
Just one man like you can make a
difference to the police force…
Actually that's my job.. -Please carry on. I will manage.
Take care.
What do we do now?
-I will decide that.
Lingam Uncle...
How are you uncle.. -Hey.. hey.
You’ve no clue how much I missed you.
-Inside the jail?
I was told that I’ve been given a ‘role’. What is it?
Yes, you’ve been given the ‘role’ of ‘Kattappa’
in the movie ‘Baahubali 2’.
Don’t make fun of me.
You have been released on ‘parole’.
You’ve been sentenced to two years of imprisonment.
I’ve battled the last six months
to get you a 4-month parole.
These four months, You must maintain good conduct.
Can you explain it in Telugu?
I am speaking in Telugu, right?
Good conduct as in well mannered.
Henceforth, you must do good to the society
and prove that you’re harmless.
The court will close your case
if they believe that you’ve changed.
What if they don’t believe?
-You’ll be sent back to jail.
Back to jail. No way! I will listen to you.
Hey, Srinu... -You’re hopeless gang is here.
Hey, Srinu...
You’re a hero, dude. -What’s all this?
Because you’ve been released from the jail.
So much for coming back from the prison.
Felicitations and cheers!
Uncle, come here. -I’m coming.
Go..
That’s irrelevant. You must tell me.
Where has mother gone?
She hasn’t gone yet. She is alive.
Where are you going?
I’ve told you so many times
not to be in the company of those boys.
Who are you to question me?
Are you trying to act big
because you are my older brother?
Have you forgotten that you’ve just come out of jail?
Don’t lecture me.
Swathi? -Mother.. Mother’s here. I’ll call you back
Why did you come back?
I thought you would go away.
I believed you would change
and take over my responsibilities.
You shattered my belief six months back.
We’ve got used to the idea of living a life without you.
It never occurs to you that
you have a brother and sister…
Your sister…
Sorry… My Daughter.
Nobody wants to marry my daughter
because her brother went to prison.
Your brother is disobedient just like you.
He is whiling away time on the roadside.
I am scared thinking of things
that could happen because you are around.
Go away.
Mother...
We don’t need you here.
Leave now.
Are you drinking because you’ve been released from the jail?
Or because your mother disowned you?
Give us some clarity.
What the hell is wrong with my mother?
Why does she expect me to be like her?
She wakes up early, does all the work at home,
packs her lunch and goes to work.
She has to salute all her superiors at work.
She is exhausted when she returns home.
At the end of the month,
she has no money left even for her bus fare.
How can one lead a life like that?
I don’t understand how they can live such a life?
If the police hadn’t caught us,
our lives would have been different.
You can be charged for drinking in a public place.
Your parole will be cancelled
and you have to serve extra time in the jail.
Where are you? -I am on Google.
I will call you tomorrow. Wind up and leave.
Where do I go?
Have you brought me to an orphanage because
I have been thrown out of my house?
This orphanage is for little children.
Not for grownups like you.
Come along.
What should I do here?
-They need a volunteer to look after the children.
If you do some good deeds, the court will close your case.
Good conduct, remember?
You’ve an interview now. Let’s go.
-An interview? Yeah.
Tell me? -Here’s the nice guy
I was talking to you about.
What were you doing before this?
I got out of jail only yesterday.
Didn’t you tell him?
Why did you tell him that you were in jail?
-You asked me to maintain good conduct, right?
I’m diabetic. I can’t take this!
Where are we going next?
You must wake up at 5 in the morning. -That early?
Listen to me...
You have to wake him up by 6 am
and get him ready by 7am.
Let's go.
At 11 pm…
Wait, When do I go to sleep?
Good Question, I will show you the bedroom.
Will I have my own bedroom?
-Yes, we shall provide with attached bathroom, come..
You call this a bedroom.
-Yes.
That is the bed and this is the room.
That’s the bathroom.
Do you like it?
You look like a ‘Clean India’ evangelist.
What happened?
This is a very difficult job.
Being in jail is easier.
Over there I have 10 people to work for me.
But here, I have to do 10 men’s work.
This won’t work out.
Find me a job where I have to work for just one person.
You have the nerve to be choosy?
Uncle, where are we going?
You asked me to look for one person, right?
I found one.
But you won’t fit the cadre.
Who are you do decide that? Let’s just go there.
Uncle... -Yes.
This is my thing. -yeah, right!
I can do this for 4 years and not 4 months.
Go inside..
How do they make so much money?
They fired so many people at once?
I stand no chance.
I should definitely get this job.
Hey, Who is he?
You don’t know him? -No.
Vikramaditya, A leading businessman. In fortune 500...
-That’s enough.
Who is that girl who followed him inside?
That’s his secretary.
Where can we find such girls?
I don’t get to see any on the road.
She is mine.
I meant the job. -The job is mine.
Rambabu.. -Sir.
Good morning sir..
Why did you choose this job?
My blood group is O Positive.
Helping people is in my blood.
I haven’t kept a photo of my mother in my house.
I’ve only hung a photo of Mother Theresa.
A lot of people have said that
they feel a ‘positive vibration’ around me.
Sudhakar.
Why did you choose this job?
I’ve been nursing a 90 years old man.
He’s passed away last week.
He said he’d miss me before he died.
He said life would be good if one had
someone like me for company.
I am soft-hearted.
I’ve also done my M.B.A.
I can also manage your business.
What is your ambition?
Money.
Humanitarianism.
Service.
Sridhar.. -Sir.
Wait. How long should I wait here?
Where do these guys come from!
Why did you choose this job?
I liked the house at first sight and
I also liked you at first sight.
Have you done this kind of work earlier?
-Do you mean social service?
I was 4. I nursed an injured dog on
the road and gave some food.
I donated blood on Powerstar’s birthday.
I donated my friend’s eyes on Superstar’s birthday.
I donated food on Rebelstar’s birthday.
I just donated something at an orphanage.
I’d never say all that.
Uncle Lingam is insisting that
I maintain good conduct and that’s why I’m here.
What’s your ambition?
I don’t have any big ambition.
I have a different one every day.
Today, my ambition is to woo her.
Can I have your phone number?
Oh.. it's alright.
Here’s my number.
I’ve free outgoing after 10. I’ll call you back
if you give me a missed call.
See ya!
What’s your name?
Srinu. -You’ve always been dependable.
Yes, Just like you.
What are you talking. Do you have sense?
You’ll say whatever you want?
Do you have any sense? Idiot.
You are appointed.
What? -You can join tomorrow.
Hey! Who are you?
Where are you going?
Who are you?
I’ve been the chief servant
of this mansion for 30 years.
A servant?
I was worried if you were the owner.
You are late on your very first day at work!
Who is this fellow?
He is the new caretaker appointed by the boss.
This fellow!
Come along.
Go and get a strong cup of coffee for me. -Get lost!
You have to wake up at 6
every morning and get ready.
Wake up the boss at 7 am and serve him coffee.
His physiotherapist will be here at 8 am sharp.
Learn all the exercises from the physiotherapist.
It will be your job from now on.
You have to serve breakfast at 9 am.
Breakfast? I already had mine.
Have this walkie-talkie with you.
You’ll be able to hear his instructions here.
You must react in no time.
There is one more important thing
that I have to say.
What is it?
Don’t waste your time following me around.
Meenakshi said the
same thing when I met her first.
Who is Meenakshi? -My ex-girlfriend.
This is your room.
Is this my room?
You have to keep the room clean and in order. -Ok.
This is your bathroom.
This looks like the ones
I’ve seen in the Hollywood movies.
Come, let us go and meet the boss.
Give me 2 minutes. -Ok, hurry up.
Why are you looking at me?
Thank you. That’s an awesome bathroom.
What are you doing?
I didn’t know he is a quadriplegic.
Thought it was only his legs.
Sir, I don’t think this fellow will last a week.
Why are you wasting your time on him?
Looking at some people, you just wish you could
spend the rest of your life here.
My job is to just take care of you. Right?
Why is she making a big fuss?
You will understand as time goes by.
Fold.. Stretch... watch carefully.
Every bone and muscle of your body must move.
You must not forget that.
He must exercise in the morning and evening.
Without fail. And be very careful, okay?
Did you get it?
Hey!
After hands... -I was doing the legs now. Not hands.
Did you notice how she is doing?
I saw everything.
-Make him sit on the wheelchair.
Lift him up.
Anything else?
Buckle him up.
You should have been careful.
-How would I know? You should have told me.
Give him a bath.
What did you say? -Give him a bath.
I can’t give him a bath.
What next?
These regulate the blood circulation in his legs.
I gave him a bath. My work ends there.
I can’t do all this.
Keerthi, he will do it.
You leave.
You can’t expect me to do everything just because
you’ve given me a luxurious bathroom.
It's alright.
Thanks.
Uncle, you didn’t tell me before.
Must brush his teeth, give him a shower, oil his hair.
I can’t do all that. Look for something else.
-Hey, idiot.
Almost everybody has rejected you.
I wonder how he liked you. Bear with it for four months.
After yoru case is closed, I’ll talk to Anwar
from Sharjah and fix up something for you.
I’m at the court. Hang up now.
Hello.. hello..
4 months?
Srinu.. Srinu...
Srinu.. -What, sir?
I want water.
Good morning, sir. -Good morning.
Hey.. Srinu!
Must send that to the lawyer, Keep it in the brown file.
That’s personal. Keep it in the black one.
What are you doing?
It’s so hot and he can’t feel a thing.
Idiot.
Are you playing with me?
Can’t you feel anything, sir?
Hello.. Okay, I’ll call back later.
Sir..
Calling you sir feels like I’m back to school.
And I always hated school.
Usually I call everyone with some relation.
Can I call you...
-What do you wanna call me?
Can I call you brother?
What’s this, brother?
Where do such girls live?
Paris. -Did you ever go?
Many times. It’s my favourite city.
Whenever I felt stressed I’d escape to Paris.
Get me a bottle of alcohol when you go next time.
You’ve so many cars parked here.
Which one should we hop into?
We’re not going in a car. We are taking the van.
This is not a van. It’s an ambulance.
You’re not a patient to commute in that.
Doctors say that
it’s not right for me to commute in a car.
You rich people, listen to your doctors and babas.
I’m not up for an ambulance. Choose a car!
Which car do you like?
Why does it sound like that, brother? -Go on.
I’m scared what he’ll do next.
It’s been an hour. How long willl you stare
at a white board with red paint, brother?
That painting is talking to me, Srinu.
I can’t hear anything.
Do you know the greatness of art?
You must tell me..
-It remains even after we’re dead and gone.
Stop it, brother. The only thing that’ll
remain is a photo frame hanging on the wall.
what’s the price? -20 Lakhs.
What?
He bought a painting worth 20 Lakhs.
Just imagine the number of pegs
I’d get in the same amount.
Hang up. I need to go.
Hello..
Hi, Vikram. -Hi.
Sorry. I’m late.
-It’s a routine for lawyers, right?
I'm not here as your company’s legal advisor.
-You had something important to say.
You selected someone I believe.
You liked him of all you interviewed?
He spilled hot water on your legs
to check if you can feel it.
Stupid fellow.  Do you know who he is?
A thief. He’s out on parole.
They are not kind and compassionate.
What if he harms you flee away, we’d be helpless.
You know your condition, right?
You should have given it a thought.
That’s it? Or there’s more?
It’s been 5 years since the accident.
Why do you all pity my life on wheelchair?
I can’t take it.
It’s annoying.
Whatever you just said to me was also out of pity.
Exactly, he doesn’t pity me.
I want that.
He asks me to talk on the phone
and completely ignores that I’m paralysed.
I don’t care about his past.
I need someone like him in my life right now.
You were saying something? About him harming me...
I’ve no hopes from my life anymore.
Why would I fear that
he will do something to me.
You never listen to me anyway.
In this world, he is of no use to anyone except you.
Srinu.
Brother?
Srinu, meet my best friend Prasad.
Sir, I think I’ve seen you before.
You’re an antagonist from Hindi dubbed films, right?
See you, sir.
Stupid fellow.
I’ve decided today, brother.
All you need is money to live the way you want.
What?
Look, your hands and legs don’t work.
Still you’re living life king size
That’s the power of money.
A painting worth 20 lakhs. That’s life!
Hey, you think I can’t do it. Now, look here.
Sorry.
Brother.
Brother, what happened?
Nothing will happen...
Nothing will happen, brother.
Brother..
I can’t breathe.
Get me out of here.
Where are we going?
-You wanted to get out, right?
I meant to the lawn.
You breathe that air all the time.
-Where are you taking me now?
They don’t sell that.
I’m scared you’ll ask its price.
What happened to you before?
It’s a minor medical issue.
-A medical problem?
Stop it, brother.
You’d feel that way if you sit in the house all the time.
You must go out sometimes.
Not just salads you must eat dum biriyani too.
Not just AC cars you must go on bike rides too.
Me? One  a bike?
You can’t hop on?
Let’s exchange our vehicles for 30 minutes
Brother, shall we ride?
You must also get a bike like this. -What?
You must get a bike..
only then will I get a chance..
Your eyes are watering because of the
wind against your face.
That’s not why my eyes are watering.
That is personal.
Did you paint? -Yes, brother. I painted it.
You paid 20 lakhs for one colour.
I used so many here. I might get 2 lakhs at least.
What were you thinking?
-An artist doesn’t reveal what he feels.
The viewer must understand that.
How is the painting?
I couldn’t find the toilet brush. Did you take it?
Get lost!
it’s like you painted it with your face.
Place it at the entrance. It’ll purge away evil’s eye.
A painter who can’t handle his pants!
He’s like a flower to my stem. Hello?
Anwar called me from Sharjah this morning.
He got me a job there.
I must go away once the case is closed.
You better take care of the arrangements.
Why are you in a hurry?
-I’ll exhaust my balance. Recharge my mobile for Rs. 500
One spicy omelette.
Are you leaving? -Not right now, After 3 months.
Vikram, you’re trying to me avoid me.
But I can’t forget you and
I know you can’t forget me either.
Oh, no!
Look. All you need is money. -Ah?
I was wondering why isn’t she falling for me.
Now you know.
What? -Didn’t you hear that? Kirthi is hitting on him.
You’ve no control on what you say.
Do you have sense?
She’s reading his letter.
What?
A letter? -Yes. A letter.
The blue one, the personal one.
The same one.
What’s the matter?
Promise me you won’t tell anyone.
Tell me quickly.
He visits these art exhibitions very often, right?
He liked a painting and
wrote a letter to an artist. Guess who she is.
Who? -A girl.
Superb.
They’ve been writing to each other
for over a year now. -And then...?
6 months ago, the girl said she likes him.
And that she wants to meet him. -Amazing.
Since then he stopped replying to her letters.
Is it? -that girl is continuing to write to him.
How can they not meet and write to each other. How?
Ask him only. -Correct.
hey.. hey.. hey.. -Trust me, I’ll take care of it.
-Stop. I beg you.
Damn, I can never keep a secret.
I hope you’ll change your mind someday.
Srinu, wait outside for 5 minutes.
What? -Wait for 5 minutes.
You must turn it off if it’s personal.
Now it’s public.
Your servant has broadcasted the information already.
Hey. -Srinu.
How dare you take the letter. Give it back.
-What’s this, brother?
Despite all the chasing she ain’t falling for me.
And you don’t care about the girl who fell for you.
That’s too much, brother. This is against the nature.
Her phone number is here.
My outgoing costs are very reasonable.
-Don’t call her, Srinu. No, don’t call her.
Please, Srinu.
Hang up. Srinu, stop it!
Srinu. -Hello.
Her voice is amazing. talk to her. -Hello.
No. -Talk!
Talk! -Hello.
Hello.. -Priya.
This is Vikram.
I’ve been meaning to call you. But couldn’t.
Just a minute. I’ll pass on the phone to Priya.
The feeling is amazing. Continue with the flow.
Talk to her. What are you doing there? Come here.
Hello..
Vikram.
Talk to her, brother.
Priya.
Vikram..
Hey, where is Vikram?
He’s busy.
He was avoiding the phone yesterday.
Today, he isn’t leaving it.
Who is it?
It’s personal.
It’ll take only 5 minutes, Please be seated.
This painting is for me? -Yes.
Yes, from where did you get?
From London. -WoW!
How much? - Two Lakhs.
How is it?
I don't understand what this artist conveying.
What is this Prasad, I expected you to recognize it.
Yes, I didn't see it properly.
Let me see.
Yes! I got it.
That Red, Yellow, Blue and Orange.
They are expressing the feelings of a Human.
Prasad, you're a Genius.
Thank you.
I'll buy it.
You know my taste. -Yes, very well.
Sir, we got the land contact and we checked it and... -
Did you call me, brother?
Yes, bring me that cover.
What’s all this, brother?
That’s the amount you got for your painting. Two Lakhs.
My painting? -Yes.
This is the first time I earned so much money.
This is the first time ever I made money.
I used to get weird feelings
when I saw white paper as a child.
To do something. To draw something.
I didn’t understand anything back then.
But now I know... No one can stop me now, brother.
No one can stop me. I’ll prove myself.
I’ll continue to paint.
It’s been really long I saw you.
Well...
(Phone ringing)
What’s this?
Srinu asked me to give this to you.
What?
Srinu asked me to give you this money.
He’ll never change.
Tell him that he’s distanced himself
a little more from the family.
I’ve been the breadwinner of this family.
And will continue to be.
We don’t need his sympathy. Leave!
I told you, right?
Your mother will never believe you.
What are you doing, dude?
What do you have to do with him?
Once again... Brother... I’ll see you in the evening.
You leave now.
Hey!
Go away!
Sir, you’ve got some mails. -Any letters?
Yes, sir. One from TIME magazine,
one from the bank and one is a wedding card.
That’s it. Anything else? -That’s all, sir.
Okay, leave me alone.
Yes sir. -Srinu.
Even you can leave.
Brother..
Were you talking about this letter?
But this doesn’t look like a letter. Is it a photograph?
Matters have moved from phone to photo.
-Srinu! Leave the letter here.
Hey, Srinu!
listen to me, Srinu.
Srinu.. No No No!
Brother, you are so done.
There’s something written behind.
Coming to Hyderabad on the 11th.
Hope we can catch up.
Hello, subtitles!
Read it in Telugu, I must understand, right?
She’s coming to Hyderabad on 11th
and was asking if he could catch up.
We are so catching up. Right, brother?
What do you think, brother?
How is it brother?
Even I thought the same, This doesn't suit.
Its not good.
This is too good.
Don’t drag the matter any further,
We must take a decision.
Srinu... -What’s it, brother?
You can’t come with me. -Why?
You talk too much.
All right, brother.
But you don’t talk too little.
Kirthi... -Yes sir.
What’s the time?
5.40 -We have 20 minutes more.
Kirthi.. -Sir?
What’s the time?
5.50
5.51, sir..
Let’s go..
There’s 5 minutes more, sir.
-I said, let’s go!
What’s it, brother? You didn’t meet her?
That’s why you asked me to stay away?
I was right there. Something’s scaring you
You’re scared of writing a letter.
Scared of talking on the phone.
You’re scared of meeting her. What’s the problem?
Srinu.
I don’t need to answer every question of you, Srinu.
Be in your limits.
Kirthi... -Sir.
let’s go.
Kirthi.. -Yes, sir
Change my phone number.
Henceforth  I don’t want Priya’s letters to reach me.
You learnt a good lesson yesterday.
Now you know how to behave with him.
Don’t annoy me. -What?
I said it. I’m gonna be in my limits.
That’s exactly why don’t do things he doesn’t like.
Oh...!
He doesn't like?
Is that why he gets you to read that girl’s letters?
He refused to talk on the phone initially
and then spoke for hours in joy.
That’s exactly why we encouraged him to meet her.
He didn’t meet her and blamed us.
These rich guys are beyond my understanding.
Tell me.
What?
Did you see?
Where are you?
I'm coming.
What happened? -I’ll see you in an hour.
Please inform him.
You would have missed the ceremony
if you got any late. -Who is he?
Look at the guy behind the guy in brown.
He’s the groom.
Who are you? What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Who are you? -Take your hand off him.
Who are you?
Who are you to question him?
You wanna know who he is. Listen to it from me..
He’ll be my husband in 10 minutes.
Mother has big dreams about your wedding.
She wont be able to take this.
What do you want me to do now?
What do I do? We pleaded his father.
They enquired about our family. What do I tell them?
That I have a brother who just got out of the prison?
Or about my rogue younger brother?
Who would accept a girl from such a family.
Will his mother accept me?
Should I ruin my life because of you guys?
Will you go talk his father?
Will you get an approval?
Look who’s talking!
Sorry!
I will talk!
You will talk? What will you talk?
What will you talk?
Swathi, he wants to give it a try.
Let him try.
We’ve waited for so long. We’ll wait for some more time.
Hey, you’re here to talk about your sister.
Be careful.
( Dog barking )
Hello, sir.
He’s our guy. -My sister...
Swathi..
Your son... -So, you’re the brother.
Yes sir.
Was wondering why the dog was barking so much.
You went to the jail I believe.
What does your mother do?
Railways... -Ah?
She’s a clerk.
Oh.. Security! -Sir.
Sir.
What’s your salary?
-Rs. 12,000 sir.
Go..
What’s your mother’s salary? 7000 or 8000?
That was a good move.
To find one from such a family and depend on him.
Whose plan was it?
Your mother’s or yours?
You want to hit me?
You are on parole I heard.
One call and you’ll be back in the prison.
Look, My dog also doesn’t like your presence.
How did you expect that I’ll accept your sister.
Go away. -Let’s go.
Sir, I’ve a small suggestion. -What?
The board outside reads beware of dog.
Add the ‘S’ let it say beware of dogs.
Hey, sit down.
Your pants are falling off.
Srinu.
Srinu.. -Yes?
What happened? -Nothing, brother.
Srinu, tell me what happened.
One must be born rich. Not like us.
We can’t do anything.
Love and relationships is only for the rich.
Not for us.
I stopped my sister’s wedding
because I'm scared for my mother.
I went to talk to him.
I couldn’t stop him
when he said things against my mother.
My mother would be very upset
if my sister married without her knowledge.
Now I know who I am.
Excuse me. -Sir?
I need to meet Mr. Kaalidaas.
I don’t care what you do. -Ok sir.
Sir Prasad Rao..
I’d have been there on order.
-I need to talk to you for 5 minutes.
Please come.
Vikram has a message for you. -Tell me, sir.
Now, you must take a call.
I need an hour from Mr. Vikramaditya. Please sir.
Greetings, sister.
May I come in?
My name is Kaalidas. I’m a small time entrepreneur.
I’ll come straight to the point.
My son likes your daughter.
He wanted to marry her but the girl wanted your approval.
Now, I like your girl a lot.
Now that’s called moral upbringing.
We can make money any time.
But good character is what a person is born with.
You just give a nod.
I know it is important to consider their wish…
But our status doesn’t match yours…
What’s the big deal about status?
Every Tom, Dick and Harry has money these days.
We shouldn’t think about these things.
The girl and boy like each other. That’s all matters.
Your daughter is now our daughter.
Just give your consent.
I will take care of everything else.
Is that a ‘yes’ from you?
Okay, sister.  We’ll see you.
Drink some coffee.
Come quickly, Swathi.
I have an important meeting to attend in an hour.
This is like my house.
I can join you for coffee at leisure.
See you again.
Let's go..
Swathi See them off.
Swathi, my child..
Are you happy now? -Yes.
Can you call your brother
right away and tell him that?
See you.
Hello..
Swathi..
I am sorry, brother.
I never treated you like my brother.
I’ve never given you the respect due to a brother.
I will never forget what you did for me today.
You’ve given me what I wished for.
Thank you, brother.
Okay, go!
You should’ve told me before itself that
you’re a close aide of Mr. Vikramaditya.
I am here because of the subcontract
he sanctioned for me.
I spoke a little too much. Please don’t mind.
I spoke to your mother.
Swathi will lead a very happy life. Forget about her.
I’ll see you.
Please don’t take anything to your heart.
What’s all this, bro?
If I’m your brother. She’s also my sister.
Just a second. It’s brother calling. What’s up, brother?
Swathi, is mother happy?
Listen to her yourself.
Yes, I'm happy.. Ok sister.
Aunt, Swathi’s marriage has been fixed.
They are very rich family.
You said we’d never get a good match for her.
Look what has happened now.
Can I talk to uncle? Pass on the phone.
He’ll get mad that I didn’t tell him.
Uncle, your grand-daughter belongs to a rich family now.
She’s very lucky.
I was so worried about her wedding.
By the blessings of almighty, I’m free of that now, uncle.
You guys must come a couple of days before the wedding.
Don’t complain later. Alright then, I’ll talk to you later. Bye.
Heard that?
Yes.
Please don’t let mother know what happened yesterday.
Okay, brother.
Since my childhood I only saw my mother suffer.
For the first time I can sense happiness from her.
It’s all because of you, brother.
Srinu. -Yeah?
Where are you going?
It’s my sister’s wedding.
I want to make money for the arrangements.
I’ll go make a few paintings.
I must hire another Prasad to sell your paintings?
Shut the door.
Lock? -I meant that.
God’s there!
you must do something for me.
I am not used to it.
But I’ll try doing whatever you say.
But not now, Later in the evening.
I can’t wait until evening. -I can’t wait either.
But we don’t have a choice.
But brother will be there in the evening, right?
-yes, he’ll be there.
He’s the main person, right?
-If he’s main. What am I ?
You’ll be there right next to him, right.
Me and brother together. No way.
But you’ll have to cut his cake, right?
Cake? -Hey, Don’t you know that it’s his birthday today?
Birthday? -We’ve planned a surprise
birthday party at a hotel this evening.
You should bring him there without his knowledge.
Please, he must not know.
You wanted to shut the door for this?
Yes, its a surprise. Not one must know.
What were you thinking?
A lot of things.
I thought the surprise was for me.
Leave!
True that.. -Go look into the arrangements.
There’s no Almighty!
Hey, where are you going?
There’s too much traffic. I’ll take a shortcut.
So, there’s a surprise party?
What are you talking about?
She told you everything?
She just can’t keep a secret.
Since 5 years they’ve been thinking
that they surprise me.
And I keep acting like I actually am.
Oh, brother!
What’s the surprise?
You will know. Let’s go.
Happy birthday! Surprise.
Prasad! What a surprise.
Srinu, even you are surprised, right?
-Beyond words.
You’ve seen nothing. The surprise is still there.
-What’s it, sir?
Amazing! Amazing!
Brother. -Uh?
You’ve been celebrating your birthday like this for 5 years?
Whose idea is this? -It’s my idea.
Expected.
What did you expect?
As a human one must have love towards art.
What would you have done? -Sir?
Silence.
It’s okay to silent while praying. But a party?
Lakshmi, wake up!
oh, no! -Turn on the lights!
hey, lights on! -hello, there’s no echo!
You go ahead!
one... one... -Who is that?
2... 2... 2... -Who are you? Come down, I say!
Hey sisters... this guys is being troublesome.
Please spare time with him.
ey ey..!
One who’d set the twin cities on fire...
Here’s presenting the dancing peacock! -Steady!
Oops! Not a peacock! -Oh!
Watch all the fun here. Have fun, boy! Music!
Do you want to have a drink?
Doctors advised otherwise, Srinu!
-Not again, brother.
Srinu! -Uh?
Thanks!
But why? -You really surprised me.
This is the best birthday I ever had!
Stop it, brother!
Srinu! -Ah?
What’s the peacock’s name?
Hahaha.. -Hahaha..
Did anyone hear that? Hahaha..
Good night, brother.
Srinu.
You’ll never leave me, right?
-I’ll never go until you ask me to.
Good night.
Good morning, brother!
It’s too late already, wake up!
Brother.. brother...
Brother!
It’s nothing but stress.
When we are stressed, we have number of things to do.
we go for a walk or jog...
But it’s very tough for him
considering his physical condition.
His body can’t take it, when he’s stressed.
If this continues, it’s going be very difficult.
It is tough to make him stress-free.
It is a boon if you are able to forget things.
God hasn’t given him that boon.
How is his health now? -He is alright now.
We will observe him for a day
and discharge him tomorrow.
Srinu, Drop me home.
That’s a nice house. Is it yours?
No, I stole it from my neighbour. -I thought as much.
You can leave now.
Are you guys Telugu?
I haven’t eaten anything from morning.
This is the first time I am coming home.
Won’t you invite me in and serve me some food?
I guessed right.
You are definitely that villain in the tele-serial.
Ok, come in.
Sit down.
How is Vikram? -He is better.
This painting… -It’s a beautiful painting, right?
Vikram bought it for me. 2 Lakhs.
What is the value you see in this painting?
Do you know anything about painting and art?
To understand art and what the artist tries to convey,
you should not decipher it in your head.
But, feel it in your heart.
So what does this artist convey to you?
Red denotes revolution and anger.
Blue denotes the hope within us.
Can you guess
why the artist has left most of it blank?
Maybe he ran short of paint.
That white space is the happiness within us.
Do you see the specks of orange scattered here and there?
Do you know what that means? -I don’t know.
Love.
Friendship
Beautiful.
Can’t believe this painting conveys so much.
Must be a great artist…
Thank you.
For what? -For helping me understand its meaning…
It's okay, Beautiful.. Let’s go.
This is imported liquor.
No, I am not. -I don’t believe that.
I am not used to having it with ice cubes.
Sir.
you were talking to the doctor
about brother’s stress or something.
What is that, sir?
What do you know about Vikram?
He sits where you make him sit.
He eats what you feed.
He sleeps when you make him lie down. That’s all?
He might be confined to a wheelchair now.
But five years back it was different.
We had to zoom on wheels to catch up with him.
You know what’s the first thing
I remember by his mention? Speed!
He loves car races and bike races,
Always up for some adventure.
He never knew what failure was. He always won.
Be it in business or a race, he always won.
That’s his quality.
However stressed he maybe,
he always had that smile on his face.
Who is this woman, sir?
Nandini his one and only love.
He was in madly love with her..
They were about to get married.
What happened?
He went to Europe for a business trip.
As usual, he was para-gliding....
You know what’s para-gliding, right?
You fly in the sky. That’s his favourite adventure.
He fell off from 150 feet height.
That's it.
Both his cervical got damaged
He went numb from his neck down.
Horrible.
When he regained consciousness,
he wasn’t worried about his condition.
He was anxious about Nandhini.
He felt it would be unfair
to get married to her and be a burden.
He made me lie to her that
he wasn’t interested in getting married to her.
He underwent treatment in Europe for six months.
He never tried meeting her again.
He let go of her thinking that it was the best for her.
He constantly thinks about her well being and happiness.
How much ever he tries to forget his past...
it keeps coming back to him like this.
He was so well. Just can’t see him in this condition.
Nothing must happen to him, sir.
God can never keep anyone happy.
He gets his entertainment from people.
He keeps troubling people for fun, sir.
He’s a bad boy!
Now I accept that you’re Telugu.
You are very emotional.
You told me so many facts when I asked.
Despite you not asking, I want to tell you one fact, sir.
I would not be at peace otherwise. -What is that?
I painted that.
I never knew my painting had
so much meaning until you told me.
But thanks for understanding and buying it.
I’ll see you, sir!
Good morning.
Vikram, How are you feeling now?
Much better. -You’ll be discharged today.
There are a couple of medicines
that you have to take for a month.
Who is looking after your medication?
What is this? -Sir.
The body might be taking
the medicines but not the heart.
So many medicines for stress?
Some alcohol at night and all
the stress disappears by morning.
You once told me that you
go to some place when you are stressed.
Which place is that?
Paris.
Can we go to Paris?
Have you gone crazy?
How can he go when he is in this condition?
Paris, Are you planning the trip for him
or for yourself?
I don’t care what you think.
You would have been to Paris many times.
But this is my only chance. Can I tag along with you?
Ok, I’ve missed seeing a lot of things in my life.
I will add one more to my list now.
That’s enough of over-acting!
We can’t take it.
Prasad.
Didn’t you tell me that Srinu is on parole?
Take care of those formalities. We are going to Paris.
How much does a ticket to Paris cost?
This is our plane.
You make it sound so normal.
Such a beautiful city, Srinu.
I agree. Very beautiful!
Paris, City of love.
Full of love…
Good morning sir. -Good morning.
Why are you so beautiful?
What?
Brother was mentioning that Paris is beautiful. Right?
Yes.
Sir..
I sat up all night and made the best plan to see Paris.
Ten o’clock is the best town to see. -Eifel Tower!
After that we can go to... -Louvre Museum...
And then we go to the music street.
And finally to the romantic river cruise.
Brother.
Have you worked as a guide here?
I love Paris, Srinu.
They’ve built such a huge cell phone tower.
I don’t think they will ever have network issues.
That is not a cell phone tower.
That’s Eiffel Tower.
Oh! They give a name even for cell phone towers.
It's so beautiful sir.. - It is..
Click a picture.
Idiot. What are you doing?
Don’t you want the tower in the background?
Just focus on me. That will do.
If you wanted a picture of only yourself,
you’ve could have got one back home.
What do you say, brother?
Only if the tower’s in the picture will
she get lots of likes on facebook, right?
That’s true.
Some people will never understand.
Srinu, let’s go!
One painting costs 50 Lakhs?
You might not get one for even 50 Crores.
I must start painting here.
Srinu, let’s go!
This is amazing. Let’s take a picture here.
Give it to me. -Hey, that’s my phone.
Brother, smile please.
Brother.
Kirthi... -Yes sir.
We are leaving tomorrow. -What, brother?
We are going back to India tomorrow.
What happened, brother?
You love Paris..
And now you want to go back?
I don’t like myself, Srinu.
For the first time I am missing myself.
When you said Paris, I was very excited.
I thought I’ll find myself.
But I just realised...
That Vikram is no more.
I can never find him again.
But one thing is true.
I realise that the heart doesn’t follow you
wherever you go.
Idiot! Stop the car.
Srinu, Don’t let them go.
Overtake that car.
Change the gear.
You want to play with us?
Lets, go. -Press the brake and then accelerate.
Kirthi, wear your seat belt.
Srinu, Right.
Go, srinu.
Shift the gear and accelerate.
Srinu, let’s go see Paris now.
Wow!
5 years ago... I met with an accident right here.
In just a second my life became a memory.
Why remember all that now, brother. Let’s go!
Srinu.. -Brother.
I want to fly!
What?
Don't worry, I am doing good.
This is madness. What are you doing..?
You should have denied, right?
-Let him do whatever he wants to do.
What is it?
No No.. Hey, leave me!
no no .. brother!
Even though your limbs don’t function..
everyone is looking at you.
I am perfectly alright. No one is looking at me.
No, brother. No!
You can tell him, right? Go, tell him!
Let him do whatever he wants to do.
That’s how you’re giving back to me? Tell him!
Hey.. No.. I'm a virgin, there is a lot see..
Hey.. I'll get heart attack please leave me.
Looks like he’s having fun!
What’s that sound? What’s with the fear?
Don’t laugh loud, brother. Kirthi can hear you.
I was very strong until now. It’s all over now, brother.
You were trying to impress her for three months.
Did she ever look at you?
No, brother. I never took it seriously.
Are you scared of taking it seriously?
Scared about what? -Then, go tell her.
I will...
I’ll propose to her with a flower.
Ki.. Kirthi..
What?
What’s with the flower?
The flower dried up. Thought I’ll change.
Are you working?
Nope. I’m sleeping. -Okay, sleep well.
I was so confident when I went.
But my heart started beating
so fast when I went closer.
That’s called fear, Srinu.
Where there’s love, there’s fear.
Fear of rejection.
Fear of loss after acceptance.
Fear of moving apart.
Truly, where there’s fear, there’s love.
Your thought is so profound.
Once upon a time you were a romantic, right?
Even now!
Even now? You’re drunk. Let’s go!
You won't believe me? -Nope.
Try me!
Pick up a girl. I’ll make her fall for me in two days.
Pick one.
What’s the bet?
What if she falls for me in two days? What’s the bet?
You decide!
If she falls for me in two days..
you must disclose your feelings to kirthi.
If she falls for you. Done. Let’s see.
Brother! he’s here.
Where do I send him again?
Give him some money and ask him to leave.
Thanks for the bike, brother. We are now done.
How do I tell that in his language?
Je t’aime.  Serre moi. Embrazze moi!
You think I cant say it?
I will do it, wait and see.
He’ll just say it. -Let him.
Je t’aime.  Serre moi. Embrazze moi!
Why are you holding my hand?
Your work is done. Leave.
Why are you falling on me?
I’m not that kind of a guy.
Don't allow him.
Why is he falling on me
when I asked him to leave?
You said.. you loved him and asked him to hug and kiss.
Me?
What’s this, brother?
Go away!
Will she come, brother?
For sure..
Will girls come on sending that flower?
You are too much!
I didn’t send her flowers.
Curiosity. - what?
Curiosity.
I don’t believe it.
She’s here.
Curiosity is here. -Why are you still here? Leave!
You knew she was coming?
You are waiting at the right place.
Jenny.
You're looking for me?
Vikram! -Ya it's me.
Is it you who sent me the flowers? -Yeah.
But why?
Beauty not admired is a sin.
You’re beautiful.
Hello, subtitles!
What?
What’s the girl saying?
-She asked why he sent the flowers?
What did brother say?
-Beauty not admired is a sin.
You’re beautiful.
This is exactly what I wanted to say.
Why did you send me flowers?
I want to go out on a date with you.
A date? -Yeah.
With you? -Don’t go by the looks.
Looks can be deceiving.
What if I say no? -Think before you say no.
You just might miss
one of the most beautiful day in your life.
It’s amazing. You know what he said...
The girl laughed. She’s fallen for him.
The game is over!
Hello.. Hello..
Why do you want to disturb them. Let’s go.
Why should I interrupt the two of you.
Two of us?
I can’t take it anymore.
Where were you hiding all these days, Jenny?
Never seen Sir so happy before.
How did you figure out that coming here
would make him so happy?
I didn’t know. My mother always said...
You’ll find where you lost.
He lost it all here. That’s why I got him here.
Is there a show happening here? -Ya.
It's your show.
My show? -Yes.
Perfect day is not over without a dance.
Will you dance with me?
Dance with you?
How is that possible? -Just dance with me.
Every breath and move you make, I'll be there with you.
Yes, It's a promise.
That was magical.
You're right,
It was one of the most beautiful days of my life.
Thank you.
Hmm..
You are like this today.
How were you before the incident?
How can any girl come like that?
How can she laugh like that?
How could she dance? The kisses... oh my!
You think I’ll forget the bet if you divert me?
What bet are you talking about?
You must go and talk to Kirthi.
It’s late. Sleep now. Good night!
You are not standing by your words.
I can’t talk like you, brother.
You must have thought about it
before accepting the challenge.
Srinu..
Just say whatever you have in your heart.
Go.
I’m going only because of you.
Srinu..
You are forgetting the flower.
Kirthi..
I need to talk to you...
Don’t turn around.
I might not be able to talk then.
I’ll tell you a truth.
I’m really scared of you.
Because I can’t match up to you...
Don’t think about our compatibility.
Meenakshi and I complemented each other,
but that didn’t work out.. right?
That means we can work out.
But Meenakshi is not as great as you. You are hot!
See..
I feared talking like this.
But brother said where there’s fear, there’s love.
I am saying it...
I
Love
You.
Hey!
you didn’t scold me.
Is that a yes?
Srinu..
Are you blind?
Just because there is a girl in front of you,
will you not see the glass?
What an embarrassment?
How will you go back to India?
He is a pain.
Hey, Where are you?
Come out..
I’ve come to visit your country
and you give me flowers.
Flowers! who sent?
where is he?
Excuse me..  I am sorry.
I am sorry. You can go!
Why are you screaming?
Despite warning him, he sent me flowers.
Are you sure he sent you the flowers? -Then?
Who else will send flowers to me?
look at the flowers closely.
I wanted to give you the flower..
Then who kept the flowers? -I kept it there.
Does that mean you heard me?
Don’t ask me
I don’t know how I liked you.
But I know the one you love will remain happy forever.
I can see that in sir.
I need that. That’s why I like you.
Hey, wait!
Are you informing me or confirming it to me?
Hey. That smile!
Brother.. I'll be right back..
Brother! -Yeah?
Srinu!
Srinu come..
Srinu.
Vikram.
Are you running away from me?
When you left me, I didn’t suspect anything.
I believed we were in love.
That moment you went away is still fresh in mind.
I thought I should never see you
or think of you again.
But when I continued thinking of you..
I was angry with myself for falling in love
with a man like you.
I began to hate you. But a week back..
Srinu called me to tell me everything.
I wondered how I stayed happy despite
of having so much hatred in me
It was only after I spoke to Srinu
Your good wishes for me were way stronger
than my hatred towards you.
How, Vikram? How can you love someone so much?
These five years, You lost yourself for me.
You were worried about me, right?
You kept away from me because
you wanted us to be happy, right?
And you are leaving without seeing that happiness?
That’s my daughter Aadhya
And my husband Abhinav.
This is my family. My happiness.
Thanks, Vikram. Thanks for meeting me.
I’d have hated you for life hadn’t you met me.
You hope to love me and not have me.
As much as you want me to be happy,
I want you to be happier than that.
Hope you make my wish come true.
How are you? I have a scent bottle for you.
-Hi, vikram.
How are you, old man?
-Who is the old man?
I saw an excellent painting for you in Paris.
Of all the things you found
a painting for me in Paris?
Lakshmi. -Sir?
I’m tired of all the salads I had in the last 10 days.
Make me some yummy stew.
Just a second, sir.
Give me that plate...
Where did I keep the plate?
Not this one, give me a bowl for stew.
You washed it properly, right?
Give me some pepper and some coriander powder..
-Lakshmi.
Why are you in such a hurry?
It’s been 5 years.
He asked me something for the first time.
I don’t have time for this. I need to serve him stew.
Get me some tamarind.
Looks like you had a great holiday. -I met Nandini.
Srinu.
Hi Sir, how have you been?
I asked him that day...
why did you choose him?
He said,
you were the right choice that moment.
I felt he was doing wrong.
But it’s my mistake.
I  saw him in this condition for
5 years and did nothing.
I told you about him for 5 minutes...
And you changed his life.
Thank you.
You’d never leave him, right?
Why would I leave a bathroom
and bedroom like this, sir.
Where would I go anyway.
I have a small doubt. -What’s that, sir?
Painting..
Did you really paint that? -You’re too much.
I trusted you and started another painting as well.
-Spare me, dude!
Sir! -Thank you very much.
Prasad knew that you painted that?
I told him, brother.
Srinu, Someone is here for you.
For me?
Who told you that I was here?
Sister told me.
Hey open your mouth, where’s your son?
He has been booked under attempt to murder case.
Your son got drunk with his friends
and got into a fight at the bar.
Two of them are in the hospital.
They are fighting for their life.
We know that you know where he is.
He better surrender himself by morning.
But if we find him, you know what’s gonna happen.
What did you do?
Tell me what happened?
I didn’t do anything.
They were having a fight.
I was just there. I didn’t hit anyone.
Okay, sit here.
Just a minute, brother.
Swathi? – Brother..
He’s with me. I’ll look after this.
You take care of mother.
This is exactly what I was worried the most about.
I lost one son already.. and now the other.
What have I done? -Mother.
Srinu! -What is it about?
You remembered us after a long time.
Kanna is in some problem. Take him to your village
He better not be seen in the city for at least 2 weeks.
-you’re coming, right?
You know I can’t go.
You come quickly. -Okay. Hey, bring the vehicle!
Do you want to sleep, brother?
-What happened, srinu?
Nothing much, brother. Just a small issue.
-Is he your brother?
Why bother about all that now?
Let’s hit the bed.
When you called me brother,
I thought you meant it.
But you hide a lot of things from me.
I don’t know.
Ok.
He is not my brother.
He is not my own brother.
Even the person I call my mother
is not the one who gave birth to me.
She is my mother’s sister.
When I was seven years old,
my parents died in an accident.
When everyone wanted to send me to an orphanage,
my aunt said she would raise me.
My sister and brother were born later.
After my uncle died,
my mother had a tough time raising all of us.
When I saw her struggling,
I would think I was an added burden to her.
I thought I would ease her troubles
by not going to school.
When she questioned me I didn’t say anything.
Ever since, we quarrelled a lot.
I wanted to do a lot for her...
I wanted to earn a lot of money to give her.
But I didn’t know how to earn it.
That’s why I started stealing.
She said me to get out of the house
I want to make money for her happiness
and not for myself.
But she never understood me.
She’s blaming me even now.
If money brings happiness,
I should be the happiest man in this universe, Srinu.
I needed a man who was just out of jail
to show me what happiness was.
Do you know where your happiness lies?
It’s with your mother.
You want to be close to your mother,
but you are distancing yourself from her.
Go away, srinu.
You can’t live alongside a wheelchair all your life, right?
Your mother needs you more than me.
You gave so much to a complete stranger like me...
imagine what you can do for your mother.
You must find where you lost, srinu.
I’ll be there in 5 minutes. Bring kanna outside.
You leave. I’m going home now.
Sir is calling.. come.
Take your brother and go home.
He is my son.
I know, it is because of him that
we are talking about marriage.
I'm here to talk about the marriage preparation.
-One minute.
Let’s fix upon a date and time
for the wedding proceedings.
You can talk to my son about it.
We’ll approve to whatever he says.
I don’t want anything. Take it off.
I said I don’t want anything. Go away!
Did you call me, sir? -Take me out.
Doctors advised otherwise, sir.
Go away!
Shall I call Srinu?
No.
Let him live his life. Don’t disturb him.
Tell me, sir..
-Can you meet Vikram?
Of course, sir..
What happened, sir?
I thought he’d miss nothing in life after the Paris trip.
But he’s missing life after you left.
He asked me not to call you..
But I got scared looking at his condition.
Go...
Brother..
What’s this, brother?
Why do you look like heartbroken kid?
Srinu..
I’m unable to breathe here. Let’s go out.
What do we do now?
Let me decide that.
See..
Just the hat and you’ll look like Quickgun Murugan.
-It doesn’t look good.
You look like a villain from Bruce Lee’s movies.
-Are you playing around with me?
It’s been long, right?
You look like Cupid now.
What will happen to the girls
if you grow your beard?
I was a plain sheet of paper.
You turned me into a painting.
When you asked me to go with my mother,
I was scared.
But when I was with her I realised..
You don’t need money to live.
Even one soul who loves you is enough
to get you through life.
What you need now is not an attender
who wipes away your tears.
But a companion
who does not let you shed tears.
That day you asked me to leave.
I am leaving now.
You can’t escape from here now.
Your hands and legs don’t move.
Your heart’s still beating.
Don’t stop it.
Hey, Srinu!
Srinu!
Srinu.
How are you, Vikram?